all right hello there adrian here but you can call me right for short so
here's a quick demo for a ghl conversations ai tab um for a client that we built and
to protect the data of the client you just use the copy of the setup so here let me ask the ai
real quick hi i want to address orientation i'm going to show you how the system will
create an appointment to the crm and capture a phone number as well
okay let's give it a few seconds
all right so let's say i'm putting ready and my phone is
bonus
okay save time and put the sync of showing it i'm gonna
um have my messages
compiled in one go so let's see how it will give us okay it asks us about the date
i'm gonna go with
okay so the aa captures that if the patients will be ready it will ask to book an appointment and
um mentioning there's 200 consult uh consult fee and yeah the booking is already captured and let's
see how it goes with the account under the crm it will place the phone number and the appointment was
okay so the
all right so the ai can also follow up based on what i uh set up the
agent and it has a human hand over auto follow up after an hour and four hours since the meta
AI can or meta can do a pop within 34 hours yeah thank you so much for watching and
you